Let's go, Sharon!
我们走,莎伦!
Careful of A.I. face-swapping!
小心A. I. 脸部擦洗!
Hi!
嗨! 嗨! 嗨! 嗨! 嗨! 嗨! Hi!
Hey, Little Rhino!
嘿,小犀牛!
Let's go play in the park!
我们去公园玩吧!
Okay, I'll be right there!
好,我马上过去!
And I will be playing in the park!
我会在公园里玩!
Don't be too late!
别迟到!
I am, Little Rhino!
我是小犀牛 小犀牛!
I can even become you!
我甚至可以变成你!
Little Rhino!
小犀牛 小犀牛 小犀牛 小犀牛 小犀牛 小犀牛 小犀牛 小犀牛 小犀牛 小犀牛 小犀牛 小犀牛
Hi, Miss Rabbit!
嗨,兔子小姐! 嗨,兔子小姐! Hi, Miss Rabbit!
Didn't you ask her on the video call to go outside and play?
你不是在视频电话上叫她出去玩吗?
Huh?
咦? Huh?
I didn't even call her!
我甚至没有给她打电话!
Looks like another case of A.I. face-swapping fraud!
看起来像又一起A. I.
Little Rabbit's in danger!
小兔子有危险了!
Let's go to the park!
我们去公园!
Split up here!
分头走!
Ox is here!
阿牛来了!
Into the supermarket!
进入超市!
Let's guard the door!
让我们守住门!
Papillon, use your equipment to find her!
帕皮隆,用你的设备找到她!
Got it!
拿到了! 拿到了! Got it!
It's time to use my new-
是时候用我的新...
For Antle to show up!
Antle出现!
Be as fake!
像假的一样!
It's Antle, disguised as Dobie with A.I. face-swapping!
是Antle 伪装成Dobie 用A. I.
Let's go!
我们走!
Kids!
孩子们!
On video calls,
视频通话后,
bad people can use A.I. to trick you
坏人可以利用人工智能骗你
by making faces of your friends and family members.
制造朋友和家人的面孔
It's good to have a secret code with our family and friends
和家人和朋友有秘密密码真好
so that we can recognize each other.
这样我们才能互相认识
Please be careful of your calls.
请小心你的电话。